<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>info on RamblingWare</title>
    <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/tags/info/</link>
    <description>Recent content in info on RamblingWare</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 22:12:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://amdelamar.com/blog/tags/info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Back Online After Migrating DBs</title>
      <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/post/back-online-after-migrating-dbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 22:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amdelamar.com/blog/post/back-online-after-migrating-dbs/</guid>
      <description>Maybe you haven&#39;t noticed, but its been a few months since my last blog post. The reason being two fold:

I migrated my blog db from MySQL to Cloudant.The WYSIWYG editor on my dashboard wasn&#39;t ready.Now that I&#39;ve got an alpha 1.0.0 version of the dashboard working, I&#39;m finally able to give an update today. 
Sorry its taken so long, but I don&#39;t work on my open source projects every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2nd Update</title>
      <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/post/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amdelamar.com/blog/post/second/</guid>
      <description>Its been quite a while, since I started my website, and now I&amp;#39;m getting back into things. I&amp;#39;ve got lots to share, and will be posting more to my other pages.
I&amp;#39;ve added 2 Projects to my Past Projects page. Senior Project and Bookmarks for Bluemix. These pages describe the overall work and results of the project. Their code won&amp;#39;t be available for download in the Code page, but I will be adding other items for others to download later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First!</title>
      <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amdelamar.com/blog/post/first/</guid>
      <description>This post marks when I started building my first blog on Wix, a website-generating factory.
Ever since I started my blog on their site, I kept getting a nagging feeling, that I wasn&amp;#39;t doing it right... I wasn&amp;#39;t programming... I was cheating. It felt wrong. I vowed that I would return to program my own website.
&amp;quot;What kind of programmer doesn&amp;#39;t create their own website?&amp;quot;, I thought.
if(\&#34;Programmer\&#34;.equals(user.getRole()) ){ return user.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>