<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>privacy on RamblingWare</title>
    <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/tags/privacy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in privacy on RamblingWare</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 14:18:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://amdelamar.com/blog/tags/privacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite 4 Firefox Add-ons</title>
      <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/my-favorite-4-firefox-add-ons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 14:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amdelamar.com/blog/my-favorite-4-firefox-add-ons/</guid>
      <description>The \&#34;mosaic killer\&#34; browser, Firefox, is my daily driver and has been for a long time. So it should be no surprise that I&#39;ve accumulated a list of favorite Firefox Add-ons (or Extensions) over the years.&amp;nbsp;
Everyone has their own favorite list, and don&#39;t think your favorite extensions aren&#39;t worthy if they aren&#39;t mentioned. But for me, personally I tend to focus on privacy and security more than your average user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Themes for ProtonMail</title>
      <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/custom-themes-for-protonmail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 21:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amdelamar.com/blog/custom-themes-for-protonmail/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve been a user of ProtonMail since 2015. Tomorrow marks my \&#34;3 year anniversary\&#34; so to speak, of when I ditched Gmail and switched to ProtonMail.
I wrote about this last year, and my reasons for dumping Gmail haven&#39;t changed.
If you&#39;re interested in taking back your email privacy, I encourage you to give ProtonMail (PM) a try. Its free to try and has more to offer now than before when I signed up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Years Without Gmail</title>
      <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/2-years-without-gmail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amdelamar.com/blog/2-years-without-gmail/</guid>
      <description>What happened?
I signed up for ProtonMail in 2015 and ditched Gmail. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using it ever since.
Why did you do that?
Mainly because of better privacy, but it has the added benefit of being highly secure.
1) Gmail is not secure in transit. Which means, when the emails are being transported from server-to-server. ProtonMail offers end-to-end encryption using OpenPGP and symmetric encryption to non-PM users.
2) Gmail is not secure at rest.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>