<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>workplace on RamblingWare</title>
    <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/category/workplace/</link>
    <description>Recent content in workplace on RamblingWare</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://amdelamar.com/blog/category/workplace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Learning at Work</title>
      <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/continuous-learning-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amdelamar.com/blog/continuous-learning-at-work/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing job interviews as of late and one question that keeps cropping up is about managing staff.
 What would you do if you were a technical manager? What would you do to improve your team and/or company?
 I&amp;rsquo;d have my folks continuously learn new skills every year.
Before I dive into my reasoning I want to preface that IBM has an internal program specifically for this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At the Office, Don&#39;t Assume Everything</title>
      <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/at-the-office-dont-assume-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amdelamar.com/blog/at-the-office-dont-assume-everything/</guid>
      <description>At the office. Its important to communicate, and assumptions are the opposite of communcation.
Assumptions lead to missed deadlines, errors, and wasted time. Someone can think that a task is being worked on since no one replied the email in the last week but is that actually true?
Here&amp;#39;s a few areas to keep in mind when working, and some reasons why it benefits you to not assume everything.
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Company needs a Web Developer</title>
      <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/every-company-needs-a-web-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amdelamar.com/blog/every-company-needs-a-web-developer/</guid>
      <description>Even if you got a website for free, and maintain it yourself, you have to admit...
You could use a web developer.
Someone to handle all the technical aspects of building, hosting, securing, designing, and maintaining your website for you or your company. A blend of SysAdmin, WebDev, WebDesigner, and Technical Support all rolled into one. If you&amp;#39;re a small company or start-up, that is. Large companies will obviously need more folks for each department, as their needs will be much greater.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>