<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>security on RamblingWare</title>
    <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/tags/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in security on RamblingWare</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 14:18:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://amdelamar.com/blog/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite 4 Firefox Add-ons</title>
      <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/my-favorite-4-firefox-add-ons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 14:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amdelamar.com/blog/my-favorite-4-firefox-add-ons/</guid>
      <description>The \&#34;mosaic killer\&#34; browser, Firefox, is my daily driver and has been for a long time. So it should be no surprise that I&#39;ve accumulated a list of favorite Firefox Add-ons (or Extensions) over the years.&amp;nbsp;
Everyone has their own favorite list, and don&#39;t think your favorite extensions aren&#39;t worthy if they aren&#39;t mentioned. But for me, personally I tend to focus on privacy and security more than your average user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTTPS Required</title>
      <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/https-required/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amdelamar.com/blog/https-required/</guid>
      <description>Its 2017, and we&amp;#39;re halfway to encrypting the entire internet.
Source: https://letsencrypt.org/stats/This is huge. Our internet communications are becoming more encrypted every day using HTTPS, also known as HTTP over TLS/SSL or HTTP Secure. The free Certificate Authority, Let&amp;#39;s Encrypt, is partly responsible because of their free service. But there is an undeniable shift in how we use the internet for our everyday lives. We depend on it more and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Years Without Gmail</title>
      <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/2-years-without-gmail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amdelamar.com/blog/2-years-without-gmail/</guid>
      <description>What happened?
I signed up for ProtonMail in 2015 and ditched Gmail. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using it ever since.
Why did you do that?
Mainly because of better privacy, but it has the added benefit of being highly secure.
1) Gmail is not secure in transit. Which means, when the emails are being transported from server-to-server. ProtonMail offers end-to-end encryption using OpenPGP and symmetric encryption to non-PM users.
2) Gmail is not secure at rest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I use Ad-Block</title>
      <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/why-i-use-ad-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amdelamar.com/blog/why-i-use-ad-block/</guid>
      <description>People hate online advertisements... Let me repeat that.
People really HATE online ads.
There are lots of online ads. And there are some that are... acceptable. Then there are the worst of offenders. The kind that sends people into fits, immediately closing the page, and leaving the website forever.
Pop-upsAuto-playing video or soundsBlinking, Floating, Shaking, or MovingDeceptive or innapropriate content. (You know what this is. *ahem* Enhancement! *ahem*)Of all the forms of advertisements, I think online advertising is the worst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You should use Two-Factor Authentication now</title>
      <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/you-should-use-two-factor-authentication-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amdelamar.com/blog/you-should-use-two-factor-authentication-now/</guid>
      <description>There were some big data leaks in 2016 that revealed millions of passwords and credentials online. LinkedIn for example had over 160 million credentials stolen from its database. If you had an account on LinkedIn before 2012, there is a near 100% probability that your email + password have been decoded, or &amp;quot;cracked&amp;quot;, already.
This is just one of the many examples over the last year. You can see a growing list here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet Security Tips</title>
      <link>https://amdelamar.com/blog/internet-security-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amdelamar.com/blog/internet-security-tips/</guid>
      <description>Alright, you know why you&amp;#39;re here. (I hope.)
You&amp;#39;ve read online about the bad things that can happen to your accounts and data. I hope you&amp;#39;ve seen some news about hackers and people losing their data, identity, money, or more. Getting &amp;quot;hacked&amp;quot; is becoming more and more common.
Credit Cards have been stolen. Accounts on Twitter, Amazon, Apple, Steam, eBay, Skype, and many, many more, have been hijacked. Millions of credentials have been leaked online for other predators to use.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>